https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/

Website Privacy Policy
Effective on January 1, 2020 Rakuten Marketing LLC dba Rakuten Advertising (hereinafter referred to as “Supplier” “we,” or “us”) operates its corporate website at https://rakutenadvertising.com (“Site”). This privacy policy describes how we collect and use personal information about you, with whom we share personal information, how we protect this information, and your rights in relation to this information. This privacy policy…...
Read More
Services Privacy Policy
Effective on January 1, 2020 Rakuten Marketing LLC dba Rakuten Advertising is an online business-to-business performance marketing company that provides services to a network of publishers and advertising brands. Those services include personalized advertising, fraud detection, facilitation of advertising-related transactions between network participants and other online advertising tools and technologies (“Services”). This privacy policy describes how Rakuten Marketing LLC dba…...
Read More
Cookie Policy
Effective on January 1, 2020 In connection with certain features of our Site and our Services, we and certain third-party business partners, vendors and advertisers may use cookies (or other technologies like clear gifs, web beacons or similar devices, including devices that function in the mobile environment) when you interact with websites, applications or advertisements in our network. Cookies are…...
Read More
Summary of Changes (Publisher Membership Agreement)
Summary of changes (EFFECTIVE January 1, 2020): Rakuten Advertising has revised its Publisher Membership Agreement (“PMA”) and has consolidated parts of our agreement.  The PMA and updated Network Policies and Guidelines will be effective at 5:00 p.m. (EST) on January 1, 2020 (“Effective Date”). You can find the revised agreement at https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/publisher-membership-agreement and a summary of the major revisions to the PMA,…...
Read More
Publisher Membership Agreement
EFFECTIVE 1/1/2020 LINK TO SUMMARY OF CHANGES Click here to view Spanish version of PMA and summary of changes. This Publisher Membership Agreement will govern your participation on the Network.  By clicking the “Accept” or similar acceptance box in any other language, you agree that the effective date of this Agreement is the date on which you click “Accept”. To print a copy…...
Read More
Tax Nexus Laws
INTERNET SALES TAX REFORM Federal and state legislative activity concerning Internet sales tax – both passed and proposed – may affect your business....
Read More
Intellectual Property Policy
Rakuten Marketing LLC dba Rakuten Advertising (“Supplier”) provides Publisher marketing networks and technology that permit independent website operators to form cooperative marketing relationships using the World Wide Web. Each Supplier network is available for use only by persons or entities that join the network as either an “Advertiser” or a “Publisher.” Supplier may provide its members with the use of…...
Read More
GDPR Addendum to PMA
Click here to view Japanese version General Data Protection Regulation Addendum to the Publisher Membership Agreement This Addendum to the Rakuten Marketing LLC dba Rakuten Advertising Publisher Membership Agreement (the “Agreement”) is by and between you (“you”) and depending on your location, either RA United States, RM Europe, RM Australia or RM Brazil as applicable.  For the purposes of this Addendum each of…...
Read More
Ad Choice Preferences
WEB BROWSER/COOKIE-BASED OPT-OUTS You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. There are also many programs that allow you to manually delete your cookies. The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads/interest-based advertising from us, our…...
Read More
Privacy Rights Request Process
Under various laws such as the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA), you have a variety of rights related to personal data which we, Rakuten Marketing LLC dba Rakuten Advertising “Supplier”, may have about you.  In order to validate your identity and to identify any personal data that we may have about…...
Read More
Affiliate Network Policies
Click here to view Spanish version  Affiliate Network Policies and Guidelines – UPDATED 9/6/18 These Network Policies and Guidelines, made effective as of September 20, 2018, are incorporated into and made a part of your Publisher Membership Agreement. All capitalized and other defined terms used herein without definition will have the meaning given to them in the Publisher Membership Agreement. As used herein,…...
Read More
Rakuten Advertising Data
At the heart of everything we do is a commitment to delivering experiences people love. All the investments we make are towards better understanding the advertising that delights consumers, and continually improving their experiences with the insights we gain. Rakuten Advertising Data pulls aggregated and pseudonymized insights from diverse resources to bring to life the patterns that shape consumer interests,…...
Read More
General Data Protection Regulation Addendum
GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION ADDENDUM TO THE AGREEMENT (Independent Controller – Data Sharing Terms) By using the Services, Supplier Technology, and/or entering into any Order Form, Company agrees to the Supplier General Data Protection Regulation Addendum to the Agreement (the “C2C Data Sharing Addendum”). Supplier and Company are each a “Party” and collectively the “Parties.” This C2C Addendum is an…...
Read More
